A Guide to the International Education Board records FA062
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1920-1960; 1
  - Foreign Countries, 2
    - England 5 - Rothamsted Laboratory of Biochemistry, 1927-1928 (Box 30, Folder 425)
    - England 6 - Imperial College of Tropical Agriculture, 1924-1926 (Box 30, Folder 426)
    - England 7 - London Mathematical Society, 1924-1930 (Box 30, Folder 427)
      Publications, endowment, meetings. G. H. Hardy, Frank Heath.
    - England 8 - Royal Veterinary College, 1924-1926 (Box 30, Folder 428)
    - England 9 - Horticultural College, Swanley, 1924-1926 (Box 30, Folder 429)
    - England 10 - Institute of Marine Biology, 1925-1930 (Box 30, Folder 430)
      Plymouth; buildings.
    - England 11 - Scientific Publications, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 431)
    - England 12 - University College, Department of Zoology and Comparative Anatomy, 1923-1932 (Box 30, Folder 432)
      Buildings, equipment, endowment. Allen Mawer.
    - England 12 - University College, Department of Zoology and Comparative Anatomy, 1923-1932 (Box 30, Folder 433)
    - England 12 - University College, Department of Zoology and Comparative Anatomy, 1923-1932 (Box 30, Folder 434)
    - England 12 - University College, Department of Zoology and Comparative Anatomy, 1923-1932 (Box 30, Folder 435)
    - England 13 - Cambridge University, School of Entomology, 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 436)
      Interrelationships of several disciplines to agricultural problems.
    - England 13 - Cambridge University, School of Entomology, 1927-1930 (Box 31, Folder 437)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 438)
      Construction, equipment, endowment. Stanley Baldwin.
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 439)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 440)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 441)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 442)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 443)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 444)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 445)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1932-1937 (Box 32, Folder 446)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University, Physical and Biological Sciences, 1932-1937 (Box 32, Folder 447)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University Accounts, 1929-1937 (Box 32, Folder 448)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University Accounts, 1929-1937 (Box 32, Folder 449)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University Accounts, 1929-1937 (Box 32, Folder 450)
    - England 13.1 - Cambridge University Accounts, 1929-1937 (Box 32, Folder 451)
    - England 13.2 - Cambridge University Library, 1926-June 1928 (Box 32, Folder 452)
      Construction, equipment, endowment.
    - England 13.2 - Cambridge University Library, 1926-June 1928 (Box 32, Folder 453)
    - England 13.2 - Cambridge University Library, July 1928-1937 (Box 33, Folder 454)
    - England 13.2 - Cambridge University Library, July 1928-1937 (Box 33, Folder 455)
    - England 13.2 - Cambridge University Library, July 1928-1937 (Box 33, Folder 456)
    - England 14 - Imperial Institute of Forestry, 1926-1928 (Box 33, Folder 457)
    - England 15 - Imperial Bureau of Mycology, 1926-1927 (Box 33, Folder 458)
    - England 16 - British Astronomical Association, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 459)
    - Finland 2 - Boys and Girls Club Work, 1925-1928 (Box 33, Folder 460)
      Local agricultural society, demonstrations.
    - Finland 2 - Boys and Girls Club Work - Reports (Box 33, Folder 461)
    - France 1 - International Bureau of Weights and Measures, 1924-1933 (Box 33, Folder 462)
      Construction and equipment. C. Guillaume.
    - France 1 - International Bureau of Weights and Measures, 1924-1933 (Box 33, Folder 463)
    - France 2 - Paris Library School, 1925-1926 (Box 33, Folder 464)
    - France 3 - Institute of Alpine Geography, 1924-1926 (Box 33, Folder 465)
    - France 4 - University Presses of France, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 466)
    - France 5 - Scientific Literature and Equipment, 1926-1928 (Box 33, Folder 467)
    - France 5.1 - University of Paris - Scientific Publications, 1926-1928 (Box 33, Folder 468)
    - France 6 - University of Paris Observatory, 1926-1927 (Box 33, Folder 469)
    - France 7 - University of Paris, Institute of Mathematical Physics, 1926-1927 (Box 33, Folder 470)
      Institut Henri Poincare. Endowment, maintenance, construction, equipment.
    - France 7 - University of Paris, Institute of Mathematical Physics, 1928-1933 (Box 34, Folder 471)
    - France 7 - University of Paris, Institute of Mathematical Physics, 1928-1933 (Box 34, Folder 472)
    - France 8 - University of Paris, Laboratory of Physical Chemistry, 1926-1927 (Box 34, Folder 473)
      Construction and equipment.
    - France 9 - Library of French Society of Biology, 1927-1929 (Box 34, Folder 474)
      Development.
    - France 10 - University of Paris, Institute of Physics of the Globe, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 475)
    - France 11 - Annual Table of Constants, 1926-1929 (Box 34, Folder 476)
      Preparation and Publication.
    - France 12 - University of Paris - Land Possibilities, 1927-1928 (Box 34, Folder 477)
    - France 13 - University of Lyons Observatory, 1927-1935 (Box 34, Folder 478)
      Endowment.
    - France 14 - Jardin des Plantes, 1925-1932 (Box 34, Folder 479)
      Construction, equipment. Louis Mangin.
    - France 14 - Jardin des Plantes, 1925-1932 (Box 34, Folder 480)
    - France 15 - Marine Biological Station, Villefranche, 1926-1928 (Box 34, Folder 481)
      Related Archival Materials note
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1023, Box 9, Folder 81.
    - Germany 0 - General, 1924-1931 (Box 34, Folder 482)
    - Germany 0 - General, 1924-1931 (Box 34, Folder 483)
    - Germany 1 - University of Gottengen, 1924-1928 (Box 34, Folder 484)
      Fellowships, Physical Institute, construction and equipment.
    - Germany 1.1 - University of Gottengen, Institute of Mathematics and Mathematical Physics, 1926-1930 (Box 34, Folder 485)
      Construction and equipment. Richard Courant.
    - Germany 2 - Waldorf School, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 486)
    - Germany 3 - Scientific Publications, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 487)
    - Germany 3.1 - University of Munich, Chemical Laboratory, 1925-1938 (Box 35, Folder 488)
      Journals.
    - Germany 4 - University of Grissen, 1925-1928 (Box 35, Folder 489)
      Experimental greenhouse.
    - Germany 5 - Collord Institute of Frankfurt, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 490)
    - Germany 6 - University of Munich, Zoological Institute, 1926-1929 (Box 35, Folder 491)
    - Greece 1 - American School of Classical Studies, Athens, 1920-1938 (Box 35, Folder 492)
      Endowment, construction, equipment, publications, excavations. K. Kuruniotis, William C. Loring, M. Carey Thomas.
    - Greece 1 - American School of Classical Studies, Athens, 1920-1938 (Box 35, Folder 493)
    - Greece 1 - American School of Classical Studies, Athens, 1920-1938 (Box 35, Folder 494)
    - Greece 1 - American School of Classical Studies, Athens, 1920-1938 (Box 35, Folder 495)
    - Greece 1 - American School of Classical Studies, Athens - Reports and Publications (Box 35, Folder 496)
    - Greece 1 - American School of Classical Studies, Athens - Reports and Publications (Box 35, Folder 497)
    - Holland 1 - University of Leiden, 1924-1926 (Box 35, Folder 498)
      Physical Laboratory, equipment. W. H. Keesom, H. Kamerlingh Onnes.
    - Holland 1 - University of Leiden, 1927-1933 (Box 36, Folder 499)
    - Holland 2 - Agricultural University, 1925-1928 (Box 36, Folder 500)
    - Holland 3 - Rijks University, Zoological Laboratory, 1926-1928 (Box 36, Folder 501)
    - Holland 3 - Rijks University, Zoological Laboratory, 1926-1928 (Box 36, Folder 502)
    - Holland 4 - Laboratory of Psycopathology, Baarn, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 503)
    - Hungary 1 - Agriculture, 1924-1926 (Box 36, Folder 504)
    - Hungary 2 - Hungarian Village Association, 1924-1929 (Box 36, Folder 505)
      Education, exhibits, library, movies, lectures; cultural, economic, social goals; current expenses.
    - Hungary 2 - Hungarian Village Association, 1924-1929 (Box 36, Folder 506)
    - Hungary 3 - Alexius De Sigmond, 1926 (Box 36, Folder 507)
    - Hungary 4 - Scientific Literature and Equipment, 1926-1930 (Box 36, Folder 508)
    - Hungary 5 - Royal Hungarian Veterinary College, 1923-1930 (Box 36, Folder 509)
      Scientific literature and equipment.
    - Iceland 1 - Boys and Girls Club Work, 1926-1927 (Box 36, Folder 510)
    - Ireland 0 - General, 1924-1928 (Box 36, Folder 511)
    - Ireland 1 - Trinity College, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 512)
    - Ireland 2 - Wesley College, 1923-1925 (Box 36, Folder 513)
    - Ireland 3 - Cyril Dickenson, 1923-1924 (Box 36, Folder 514)
      Agricultural cooperative movement.
    - Italy 0 - General, 1924-1937 (Box 36, Folder 515)
    - Italy 1 - Naples Zoological Station, 1924-1925 (Box 36, Folder 516)
      Fellowships, current expenses. Reinhard Dohrn, T. H. Morgan.
    - Italy 1 - Naples Zoological Station, 1926-1931 (Box 37, Folder 517)
    - Italy 1 - Naples Zoological Station, 1926-1931 (Box 37, Folder 518)
    - Italy 1 - Naples Zoological Station, 1926-1931 (Box 37, Folder 519)
    - Italy 2 - Agriculture, 1924-1925 (Box 37, Folder 520)
    - Italy 3 - Teacher Training - Rural Schools, 1924-1928 (Box 37, Folder 521)
      Vocational agriculture teacher study. Alessandro Marcucci.
    - Italy 3 - Teacher Training - Rural Schools, 1924-1928 (Box 37, Folder 522)
    - Italy 4 - Scientific Publications, 1924-1926 (Box 37, Folder 523)
    - Italy 4.1 - Italian Scientific Journals, 1925-1930 (Box 37, Folder 524)
      Lincei.
    - Italy 5 - Marine Biological Station, Rovigno, 1925-1930 (Box 37, Folder 525)
    - Italy 7 - American Academy in Rome, 1926-1931 (Box 37, Folder 526)
      Endowment, construction, equipment; humanities, classical studies, fine arts, music. William A. Boring.
    - Italy 7 - American Academy in Rome - Reports (Box 37, Folder 527)
    - Italy 7 - American Academy in Rome - Reports (Box 37, Folder 528)
    - Italy 7 - American Academy in Rome - Reports (Box 38, Folder 529)
    - Italy 7 - American Academy in Rome - Publications (Box 38, Folder 530)
    - Italy 7 - American Academy in Rome - Publications (Box 38, Folder 531)
    - Japan 0 - General, 1925-1928 (Box 38, Folder 532)
    - Japan 1 - Hokkaido Imperial University, Sapporo, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 533)
    - Java 0 - General, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 534)
    - Jugoslavia 0 - General, 1925-1931 (Box 38, Folder 535)
    - Jugoslavia 1 - University of Zagreb, 1924-1926 (Box 38, Folder 536)
    - Jugoslavia 1.1 - University of Zagreb, Laboratory of Plan Physiology, 1927-1928 (Box 38, Folder 537)
    - Latvia 0 - General, 1925-1927 (Box 38, Folder 538)
    - Lithuania 0 - General, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 539)
    - Lithuania 1 - University of Kaunas, Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 540)
    - Mexico 0 - General, 1923-1928 (Box 38, Folder 541)
    - Mexico 1 - American School Foundation, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 542)
    - Mexico 2 - American College, Mexico City, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 543)
    - Mexico 3 - National Preparatory School, Mexico City, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 544)
    - Mexico 4 - Alfonso Pruneda, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 545)
    - Mexico 5 - National University of Mexico, Mexico City, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 546)
    - Mexico 6 - Secondary Education, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 547)
    - New Zealand 0 - General, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 548)
    - New Zealand 1 - Cawthron Institute of Scientific Research, 1924-1926 (Box 38, Folder 549)
    - Norway 0 - General, 1924-1929 (Box 39, Folder 550)
    - Norway 0 - General, 1924-1929 (Box 39, Folder 551)
    - Norway 1 - Norwegian Observatory, 1925-1933 (Box 39, Folder 552)
      Aurora Institute, construction, land, equipment.
    - Norway 1 - Norwegian Observatory, 1925-1933 (Box 39, Folder 553)
    - Norway 2 - Fram Kursus Institute, 1925-1926 (Box 39, Folder 554)
      Agricultural education, rural correspondence courses. T. Norstraum.
    - Norway 4 - Maritime Museum and Institute, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 555)
    - Philippine Islands 0 - General, 1926-1936 (Box 39, Folder 556)
    - Philippine Islands 1 - Bureau of Educational Research, 1923-1936 (Box 39, Folder 557)
      Methods of teaching English to natives. Arthur Woods, Dwight F. Davis, J. R. Hayden, E. A. Gilmore.
    - Philippine Islands 1 - Bureau of Educational Research, 1923-1936 (Box 39, Folder 558)
    - Philippine Islands 2 - Proposed Research Institute, 1927-1930 (Box 39, Folder 559)
    - Poland 0 - General, 1924-1931 (Box 39, Folder 560)
    - Poland 1 - Warsaw Academy of Science, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 561)
    - Poland 4 - Scientific Literature, 1926-1929 (Box 40, Folder 562)
    - Poland 5 - University of Cracow, Biological Institute, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 563)
    - Portugal 0 - General, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 564)
    - Roumania 0 - General, 1925-1931 (Box 40, Folder 565)
    - Russia 0 - General, 1925-1928 (Box 40, Folder 566)
    - Russia 1 - Experiment Station for Soil Science, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 567)
    - Scotland 0 - General, 1925-1932 (Box 40, Folder 568)
    - Scotland 1 - University of Edinburgh, Department of Animal Breeding, 1925-1935 (Box 40, Folder 569)
      Endowment, buildings, equipment. F. A. E. Crew, Alfred Ewing.
    - Scotland 1 - University of Edinburgh, Department of Animal Breeding, 1925-1935 (Box 40, Folder 570)
    - Scotland 1 - University of Edinburgh, Department of Animal Breeding, 1925-1935 (Box 40, Folder 571)
    - Scotland 3 - Soil Surveyor, 1924-1926 (Box 40, Folder 572)
      Surveys and lectures. Robert Greig, J. O. Veatch.
    - Scotland 4 - University of Edinburgh, Department of Zoology, 1926-1936 (Box 40, Folder 573)
      Construction, equipment and endowment. J. H. Ashworth.
    - Serbia 0 - General, 1924-1925 (Box 40, Folder 574)
    - Siam 0 - General, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 575)
    - Spain 0 - General, 1923-1932 (Box 41, Folder 576)
    - Spain 1 - Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1923-1939 (Box 41, Folder 577)
      Council for the Extension of Research and Scientific Investigations. Construction and equipment. Blas Cabrera, Jose Maria Torrojz, Jose Castillejo.
    - Spain 1 - Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1923-1939 (Box 41, Folder 578)
    - Spain 1 - Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1923-1939 (Box 41, Folder 579)
    - Spain 1 - Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1923-1939 (Box 41, Folder 580)
    - Spain 1 - Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1923-1939 (Box 41, Folder 581)
    - Spain 1 - Institute of Physics and Chemistry - Reports (Box 41, Folder 582)
    - Sweden 0 - General, 1925-1927 (Box 41, Folder 583)
    - Sweden 1 - University of Stockholm, Mathematical Institute, 1924-1928 (Box 41, Folder 584)
    - Sweden 2 - Boys and Girls Club Work, 1924-1928 (Box 41, Folder 585)
    - Sweden 2.1 - Boys and Girls Club Work - Reports (Box 41, Folder 586)
    - Sweden 3 - Upsala, Physical Institute, 1925-1935 (Box 41, Folder 587)
      Equipment, fellowships. Manne Siegbahn.
    - Sweden 4 - University of Stockholm, Biochemical Institute, 1926-1934 (Box 42, Folder 588)
      Construction and equipment. H. von Euler.
    - Sweden 5 - Central Institute for Agricultural Research, 1926-1929 (Box 42, Folder 589)
    - Sweden 6 - University of Upsala, Laboratory of Physical Chemistry, 1927-1931 (Box 42, Folder 590)
    - Switzerland 0 - General, 1926-1928 (Box 42, Folder 591)
    - Switzerland 1 - Botanical Conservatory, Geneva, 1926-1930 (Box 42, Folder 592)
      Library museum.
    - Switzerland 2 - University of Zurich, Chemical Laboratory Equipment, 1926-1930 (Box 42, Folder 593)
    - Switzerland 3 - High Altitude Station of the Jungfrau, 1928-1931 (Box 42, Folder 594)
      Construction and equipment. Interdisciplinary cooperation. W. R. Hess.
    - Turkey 0 - General, 1920-1927 (Box 42, Folder 595)
    - Wales 0 - General, 1925-1928 (Box 42, Folder 596)
  - Fellowships in Science, 3
    This subseries consists of fellowship files in the physical and natural sciences. Fellowships in the Far East are listed at the end of this subseries.
    - Fellowships in Science, 1923-1925 (Box 42, Folder 597)
      Administration, National Research Council (NRC), interviews.
    - Fellowships in Science, 1923-1925 (Box 42, Folder 598)
    - Fellowships in Science, 1923-1925 (Box 42, Folder 599)
    - Fellowships in Science, 1923-1925 (Box 42, Folder 600)
    - Fellowships in Science, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 601)
    - Fellowships in Science, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 602)
    - Fellowships in Science, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 603)
    - Fellowships in Science, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 604)
    - Fellowships in Science - General Policy, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 605)
    - Fellowships in Science - General Policy, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 606)
    - Fellowships in Science - General Policy, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 607)
    - Fellowships in Science - General Policy, 1925-1929 (Box 43, Folder 608)
    - Marcil Abeloos, 1928-1939 (Box 43, Folder 609)
    - Leo Abalins, 1925-1928 (Box 43, Folder 610)
    - Wilhelm Ackerman, 1924-1926 (Box 43, Folder 611)
      Mathematics.
    - Donald Keith Adams, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 612)
      Psychology.
    - Howard B. Adelman, 1926-1938 (Box 44, Folder 613)
      Embryology.
    - S. S. Aiyar, 1924 (Box 44, Folder 614)
      Referred.
    - Werner Albrecht, 1927-1933 (Box 44, Folder 615)
      Magnetic-chemistry.
    - Paul Alexandroff, 1924-1928 (Box 44, Folder 616)
    - S. K. Allison, 1925-1934 (Box 44, Folder 617)
      Withdrew.
    - Henri A. P. Allorge, 1926-1927 (Box 44, Folder 618)
      Declined.
    - Viladimir Alpatov, 1926-1929 (Box 44, Folder 619)
      Biometrics.
    - Herbert Alyea, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 620)
    - Elod Anderlik, 1925-1934 (Box 44, Folder 621)
      Aerodynamics.
    - Edgar Anderson, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 622)
    - Donald Hatch Andrews, 1924-1933 (Box 44, Folder 623)
    - W. E. Ankel, 1924 (Box 44, Folder 624)
    - Igor N. Ashehov, 1924 (Box 44, Folder 625)
    - Peter Ashmarin, 1924-1925 (Box 44, Folder 626)
    - Robert Atkinson, 1926-1932 (Box 44, Folder 627)
    - William L. Ayres, 1927-1929 (Box 44, Folder 628)
    - Walter Baade, 1925-1934 (Box 44, Folder 629)
    - Werner Bachmann, 1927-1933 (Box 44, Folder 630)
      Organic chemistry.
    - Richard M. Badger, 1927-1929 (Box 44, Folder 631)
    - Jean G. Baer, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 632)
      Parasitology.
    - Stefan Banach, 1924-1934 (Box 44, Folder 633)
    - Torn Barth, 1928-1930 (Box 44, Folder 634)
      Minerology.
    - Nina Bary, 1928-1934 (Box 44, Folder 635)
    - Lawrence W. Bass, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 636)
      Biochemistry.
    - John R. Bates, 1927-1933 (Box 44, Folder 637)
    - Victor Bauer, 1924-1926 (Box 44, Folder 639)
      Marine biology.
    - Karl Bechert, 1925-1933 (Box 44, Folder 640)
      Spectroscopy.
    - Heinrich Behmann, 1925-1926 (Box 44, Folder 641)
    - Birger M. Bergenson, 1925-1935 (Box 45, Folder 642)
    - N. J. Berrill, 1926-1932 (Box 45, Folder 643)
    - Abram Besicovitch, 1924-1930 (Box 45, Folder 644)
    - M. K. Biernacki, 1928 (Box 45, Folder 645)
    - J. M. Bijvoet, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 646)
    - Francis Bitter, 1926 (Box 45, Folder 647)
      National Research Council (NRC).
    - S. C. Bochner, 1925-1937 (Box 45, Folder 648)
    - C. G. Boissonas, 1926-1935 (Box 45, Folder 649)
      Physical chemistry.
    - Otakar Boruvka, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 650)
    - Hilbrand Boschma, 1925-1927 (Box 45, Folder 651)
    - Arabinda M. Bose, 1924 (Box 45, Folder 652)
    - Richard Boylan, 1927-1932 (Box 45, Folder 653)
    - Emil Bosler, 1927-1928 (Box 45, Folder 654)
    - F. W. Rogers Brambell, 1926-1928 (Box 45, Folder 655)
    - Geza Braun, 1926-1934 (Box 45, Folder 656)
    - Karl Brauner, 1928-1932 (Box 45, Folder 657)
      Geometry.
    - Leo Brauner, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 658)
      Geoelectric phenomena.
    - Marcel Brelot, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 659)
    - Friedrich Brieger, 1924-1928 (Box 45, Folder 660)
      Plant genetics.
    - David R. Briggs, 1928-1930 (Box 45, Folder 660A)
    - R. A. Brink, 1925-1929 (Box 45, Folder 661)
    - Robert B. Brode, 1925-1935 (Box 45, Folder 662)
    - Dirk Brouwer, 1927-1934 (Box 45, Folder 663)
    - Junius Brown, 1929 (Box 46, Folder 664)
    - Arthur Brozek, 1924-1937 (Box 46, Folder 665)
    - Wilhelm Buchman, 1925-1931 (Box 46, Folder 666)
    - W. H. Burgers, 1924-1928 (Box 46, Folder 667)
    - Dean T. Burk, 1927-1928 (Box 46, Folder 668)
    - Aladar Buzagh, 1927-1938 (Box 46, Folder 669)
    - Fernando Calvet Prats, 1928 (Box 46, Folder 670)
    - Brunther Carlo, 1927-1932 (Box 46, Folder 671)
    - J. Carl, 1925 (Box 46, Folder 672)
    - Miguel Catalan, 1924-1937 (Box 46, Folder 673)
    - Maurice Chazel, 1925 (Box 46, Folder 674)
    - William Childs, 1929 (Box 46, Folder 675)
    - Eugen Chirnoaga, 1926-1927 (Box 46, Folder 676)
    - Alonzo Church, 1927-1929 (Box 46, Folder 677)
    - Anthony Claassen, 1925 (Box 46, Folder 678)
    - William Clarkson, 1927-1932 (Box 46, Folder 679)
    - Kenneth Cole, 1928 (Box 46, Folder 680)
      Physiology.
    - Edward Condon, 1926-1938 (Box 46, Folder 681)
    - Sherburne F. Cook, 1926-1929 (Box 46, Folder 682)
    - Ralph Cornwell, 1926 (Box 46, Folder 683)
    - Frank Cortese, 1926-1929 (Box 46, Folder 684)
    - Joseph L. Costa, 1924-1926 (Box 46, Folder 685)
    - E. H. Craigie, 1926-1937 (Box 46, Folder 686)
    - Umberto D'Ancona, 1924-1926 (Box 46, Folder 687)
      Comparative anatomy.
    - Paul Davidovitch, 1924-1933 (Box 47, Folder 688)
    - Constantin Dawydoff, 1926-1932 (Box 47, Folder 689)
    - Siebe R. deBoer, 1927-1931 (Box 47, Folder 690)
    - T. L. deBruin, 1926-1931 (Box 47, Folder 691)
    - Jan Dembrowski, 1924-1928 (Box 47, Folder 692)
    - Ladislas Demeny, 1925-1934 (Box 47, Folder 693)
    - W. E. de Mal, 1924-1936 (Box 47, Folder 694)
      Heredity.
    - David Dennison, 1924-1929 (Box 47, Folder 695)
    - Jane Dewey, 1925-1928 (Box 47, Folder 696)
    - Roscoe Dickenson, 1924-1928 (Box 47, Folder 697)
    - Gerhard Dieki, 1925-1927 (Box 47, Folder 698)
    - Theodosius Dobzhansky, 1927-1929 (Box 47, Folder 699)
    - Jesse Douglas, 1926-1936 (Box 47, Folder 700)
    - Julius F. Dubourdieu, 1927-1929 (Box 47, Folder 701)
    - Paul Dubreil, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 702)
    - Andrew Dudich, 1924-1935 (Box 47, Folder 703)
    - Filippo Dulzetto, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 704)
    - Hans Dluus, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 705)
    - E. G. Dymond, 1924-1931 (Box 48, Folder 706)
    - Ludwig Ebert, 1924-1928 (Box 48, Folder 707)
    - Carl Echart, 1926-1929 (Box 48, Folder 708)
    - Aristotle Economou, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 709)
    - Kurt Ehrenberg, 1924-1930 (Box 48, Folder 710)
    - Maximilian Ehrenstein, 1924-1926 (Box 48, Folder 711)
    - Albert Einstein, 1924 (Box 48, Folder 712)
      Assistant.
    - Per Ekwall, 1929-1931 (Box 48, Folder 713)
    - Paslo Enriques, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 714)
    - Boris Ephrussi, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 715)
    - Carl Epling, 1926-1933 (Box 48, Folder 716)
    - Henry Eyring, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 717)
    - Hans Falkenhagen, 1927 (Box 48, Folder 718)
    - Gerhard Fankhauser, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 719)
    - Jean Favard, 1925-1932 (Box 48, Folder 720)
    - Albert Fellows, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 721)
    - Lucien Ferand, 1928-1934 (Box 48, Folder 722)
    - Enrico Fermi, 1924-1928 (Box 48, Folder 723)